{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"8.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1170,"frameRate":30},"ContentStructure":[{"id":"si1251","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","title":"Privacy and Security Awareness Week ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"Test your privacy and security knowledge with these skill testing questions! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Brought to you by the OCIO Information Security in partnership with Health Information Privacy, Security and Legislation ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_1","Text_Caption_2","Image_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"si4575","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4504","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What definition appropriately describes the privacy term “disclosure”? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4519","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4523","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"This is what you do with information you gathered within the Ministry ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4519a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"This is what you do with information you gathered within the Ministry\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si4530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4534","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"This is the process of gathering information for a particular authorized purpose ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4530a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"This is the process of gathering information for a particular authorized purpose\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6169","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6173","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"This is what occurs when personal information that has been collected by the Ministry is shared outside the Ministry ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6169a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"This is what occurs when personal information that has been collected by the Ministry is shared outside the Ministry\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si4571","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4579","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide4471q0","for":"Slide4471q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide4471q0","for":"Slide4471q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide4471q0","for":"Slide4471q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide4471q0","for":"Slide4471q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4538","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  C. Disclosure of information occurs when personal information that has been collected by the Ministry is shared outside the Ministry. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6177","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry!  Correct answer  C. Disclosure of information occurs when personal information that has been collected by the Ministry is shared outside the Ministry. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4471","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si4497","si4504","si4523","si4534","si6173","si4579","si4593","si4607","si4621","si4560"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4471"},"question":{"interactionId":"4484","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si4718","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4661","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What is the standard document required by government bodies to assess the privacy impacts of any new project, program or activity? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4683","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4687","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"An information sharing agreement (ISA) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4683a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"An information sharing agreement (ISA)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si4694","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4698","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A Privacy Impact Assessment (PIA) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4694a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A Privacy Impact Assessment (PIA)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A Security Threat and Risk Assessment (STRA) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6188a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A Security Threat and Risk Assessment (STRA)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6203","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6207","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Different documents are required depending on the project ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6203a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Different documents are required depending on the project\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si4714","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide4635q1","for":"Slide4635q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4736","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide4635q1","for":"Slide4635q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4750","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide4635q1","for":"Slide4635q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4764","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide4635q1","for":"Slide4635q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct!  Correct answer  B. FOIPPA requires that a PIA be conducted for any new system, project, program or activity, or proposed enactment, or when making changes to an existing one.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4706","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, nice try!   Correct answer  B. FOIPPA requires that a PIA be conducted for any new system, project, program or activity, or proposed enactment, or when making changes to an existing one.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4710","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4635","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si4661","si4668","si4687","si4698","si6192","si6207","si4722","si4736","si4750","si4764","si4710"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4635"},"question":{"interactionId":"4648","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What is the standard document required by government bodies to assess the privacy impacts of any new project, program or activity?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si4861","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4804","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4811","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Who is responsible for completing a Privacy Impact Assessment? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4826","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Office of the Chief Information Officer (OCIO) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4826a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Office of the Chief Information Officer (OCIO)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si4837","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4841","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Program area responsible for the project ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4837a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Program area responsible for the project\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6218","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Health Information Privacy, Security & Legislation Branch ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6218a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Health Information Privacy, Security & Legislation Branch\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si4857","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4865","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide4778q2","for":"Slide4778q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4879","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide4778q2","for":"Slide4778q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4893","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide4778q2","for":"Slide4778q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide4778q2","for":"Slide4778q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer – B. While the Health Information Privacy, Security and Legislation branch will help to author the PIA, program areas are ultimately responsible for completing it.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4849","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry!  Correct answer – B. While the Health Information Privacy, Security and Legislation branch will help to author the PIA, program areas are ultimately responsible for completing it.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4778","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si4804","si4811","si4830","si4841","si6222","si4865","si4879","si4893","si4907","si4853"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4778"},"question":{"interactionId":"4791","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Who is responsible for completing a Privacy Impact Assessment?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5004","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4947","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4954","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Who should you contact for help on Privacy Impact Assessments and Security Threat and Risk Assessments? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4969","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4973","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Office of the Chief Information Officer (OCIO) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4969a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Office of the Chief Information Officer (OCIO)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si4980","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Health Information Privacy, Security & Legislation Branch (HIPSL) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4980a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Health Information Privacy, Security & Legislation Branch (HIPSL)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6252","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Data Management Stewardship (DMS) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6248a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Data Management Stewardship (DMS)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5000","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5008","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide4921q3","for":"Slide4921q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5022","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide4921q3","for":"Slide4921q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5036","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide4921q3","for":"Slide4921q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide4921q3","for":"Slide4921q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4988","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  B. You can contact the HIPSL privacy team for assistance completing a PIA at HealthInformationPrivacy@gov.bc.ca and the HIPSL security team for completing a STRA at HLTHInfoSec@gov.bc.ca. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4992","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, nice try! Correct answer  B. You can contact the HIPSL privacy team for assistance completing a PIA at HealthInformationPrivacy@gov.bc.ca and the HIPSL security team for completing a STRA at HLTHInfoSec@gov.bc.ca. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4921","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si4947","si4954","si4973","si4984","si6252","si5008","si5022","si5036","si5050","si4996"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4921"},"question":{"interactionId":"4934","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Who should you contact for help on Privacy Impact Assessments and Security Threat and Risk Assessments?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5147","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Which of the following best describes the data access principles of “Least Privilege” and “Need to Know”?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5112","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5116","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The two highest security classifications for documents on records ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5112a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The two highest security classifications for documents on records\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5123","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5127","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Top-down data access models that provide management staff with full access to all information and records ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5123a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Top-down data access models that provide management staff with full access to all information and records\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ensuring access to sensitive information is given only to those that require it as part of their role, and that access is restricted to only the information required to perform specific duties or tasks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6270a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensuring access to sensitive information is given only to those that require it as part of their role, and that access is restricted to only the information required to perform specific duties or tasks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6285","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"None of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6285a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"None of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5143","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5151","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5064q4","for":"Slide5064q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5064q4","for":"Slide5064q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5179","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5064q4","for":"Slide5064q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5193","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5064q4","for":"Slide5064q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5131","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  C.  “Need to Know” is a privacy principle where access is restricted to authorized individuals whose duties require such access. Individuals are not entitled to access merely because of status, rank or office. “Least Privilege” is a security principle requiring that each subject in a system be granted the most restrictive set of privileges (or lowest clearance) needed for the performance of authorized tasks.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5135","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry!  Correct answer  C.  “Need to Know” is a privacy principle where access is restricted to authorized individuals whose duties require such access. Individuals are not entitled to access merely because of status, rank or office. “Least Privilege” is a security principle requiring that each subject in a system be granted the most restrictive set of privileges (or lowest clearance) needed for the performance of authorized tasks.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5139","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5064","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5090","si5097","si5116","si5127","si6274","si6289","si5151","si5165","si5179","si5193","si5139"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5064"},"question":{"interactionId":"5077","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following best describes the data access principles of “Least Privilege” and “Need to Know”? \r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5290","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5233","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5240","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What is “data aggregation”?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5255","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5259","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Compiling multiple sources of data into a single data set ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5255a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Compiling multiple sources of data into a single data set\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5266","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Expressing data in summary form for purposes such as statistical analysis ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5266a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Expressing data in summary form for purposes such as statistical analysis\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6300","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6304","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Transforming ordinary information into unintelligible text ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6300a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Transforming ordinary information into unintelligible text\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5286","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5207q5","for":"Slide5207q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5207q5","for":"Slide5207q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5207q5","for":"Slide5207q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5336","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5207q5","for":"Slide5207q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  B.  Aggregating data involves grouping data around specific variables such as age, gender or region to enable statistical analysis without providing personally identifiable information such as name or address. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, nice try!  Correct answer  B.  Aggregating data involves grouping data around specific variables such as age, gender or region to enable statistical analysis without providing personally identifiable information such as name or address.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5207","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5233","si5240","si5259","si5270","si6304","si5294","si5308","si5322","si5336","si5282"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5207"},"question":{"interactionId":"5220","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5433","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5383","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Does de-identified and aggregate data have to be treated like personal or sensitive information? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5398","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5402","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Always ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5398a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Always\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5409","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5413","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Never ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5409a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Never\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6315","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sometimes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6315a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sometimes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5429","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5437","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5350q6","for":"Slide5350q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5451","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5350q6","for":"Slide5350q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5465","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5350q6","for":"Slide5350q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5479","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5350q6","for":"Slide5350q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer - C  When de-identified or aggregate data has a high potential for re-identification with personal information, it must be treated as personal information.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry! Correct answer - C  When de-identified or aggregate date has a high potential for re-identification with personal information, it must be treated as personal information. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5350","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5376","si5383","si5402","si5413","si6319","si5437","si5451","si5465","si5479","si5425"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5350"},"question":{"interactionId":"5363","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5576","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5519","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5526","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Who should employees contact for help on requesting access to Ministry of Health Data? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5541","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Health Information Privacy, Security & Legislation Branch (HIPSL) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5541a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Health Information Privacy, Security & Legislation Branch (HIPSL)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5552","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5556","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Information Technology Services Branch (ITSB) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5552a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Information Technology Services Branch (ITSB)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6330","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Data Management and Stewardship (DMS) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6330a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Data Management and Stewardship (DMS)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5572","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5493q7","for":"Slide5493q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5493q7","for":"Slide5493q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5493q7","for":"Slide5493q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5493q7","for":"Slide5493q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  C.   You can contact DMS’ Access Audits and Agreements (healthdatacentral@gov.bc.ca) for help on requesting access to MOH data. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5564","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, nice try! Correct answer  C.  You can contact DMS’ Access Audits and Agreements (healthdatacentral@gov.bc.ca) for help on requesting access to MOH data. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5493","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5519","si5526","si5545","si5556","si6334","si5580","si5594","si5608","si5622","si5568"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5493"},"question":{"interactionId":"5506","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Who should employees contact for help on requesting access to Ministry of Health Data?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5719","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What type of agreement is normally used to outline the terms and conditions for the regular, systematic sharing of data with someone outside of the ministry? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5684","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5688","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"An Information Sharing Agreement ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5684a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"An Information Sharing Agreement\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5695","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5699","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A Data Management Agreement ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5695a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A Data Management Agreement\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6345","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A Service Agreement ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6345a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A Service Agreement\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6364","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Contract Schedule G ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6360a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contract Schedule G\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5715","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5636q8","for":"Slide5636q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5636q8","for":"Slide5636q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5751","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5636q8","for":"Slide5636q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5765","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5636q8","for":"Slide5636q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5703","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  A.  Information Sharing Agreements are normally used for regular, systematic exchanges of personal or sensitive information.  Contact DMS’ Access Audits and Agreements (healthdatacentral@gov.bc.ca) for more information. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5707","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry! Correct answer  A.  Information Sharing Agreements are normally used for regular, systematic exchanges of personal or sensitive information.  Contact DMS’ Access Audits and Agreements (healthdatacentral@gov.bc.ca) for more information. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5636","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5662","si5669","si5688","si5699","si6349","si6364","si5723","si5737","si5751","si5765","si5711"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5636"},"question":{"interactionId":"5649","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What type of agreement is normally used to outline the terms and conditions for the regular, systematic sharing of data with someone outside of the ministry?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5862","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5805","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5812","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"It is OK to use the same password on more than one website as long as it contains a complex mix of letters, numbers and symbols. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5827","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5827a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5838","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5838a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5858","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5779q9","for":"Slide5779q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5779q9","for":"Slide5779q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5779q9","for":"Slide5779q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5908","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5779q9","for":"Slide5779q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5846","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer - False  Hackers do have a tougher time cracking long passwords with a mix of letters, numbers and special characters. But if your password gets stolen and you have used it for multiple accounts, someone could immediately access those other accounts before you realize what is happening. Do not use the same password for all of your accounts or online access points. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5850","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry! Correct answer - False  Hackers do have a tougher time cracking long passwords with a mix of letters, numbers and special characters. But if your password gets stolen and you have used it for multiple accounts, someone could immediately access those other accounts before you realize what is happening. Do not use the same password for all of your accounts or online access points. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5854","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5779","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5805","si5812","si5831","si5842","si5866","si5880","si5894","si5908","si5854"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5779"},"question":{"interactionId":"5792","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"It is OK to use the same password on more than one website as long as it contains a complex mix of letters, numbers and symbols.\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6005","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5955","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ransomware is usually delivered in e-mails with malicious attachments. Which file extensions are dangerous? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5974","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"doc, .docx, .xls, .ppt, .pptx ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5970a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"doc, .docx, .xls, .ppt, .pptx\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5981","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":".exe, .zip, .js, .scr ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5981a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":".exe, .zip, .js, .scr\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6379","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6375a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6001","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6009","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5922q10","for":"Slide5922q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6023","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide5922q10","for":"Slide5922q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6037","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide5922q10","for":"Slide5922q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6051","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide5922q10","for":"Slide5922q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5989","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! Correct answer  C  A dangerous file category to watch out for is Microsoft Office Files (.doc, .docx, .xls, .xlsx, .ppt, and so forth). They may contain vulnerable macros. Other suspicious files are executables (like .exe or .scr), with Visual Basic scripts or JavaScript (.vbs and .js) not far behind.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5993","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect, sorry! Correct answer  C.  A dangerous file category to watch out for is Microsoft Office Files (.doc, .docx, .xls, .xlsx, .ppt, and so forth). They may contain vulnerable macros. Other suspicious files are executables (like .exe or .scr), with Visual Basic scripts or JavaScript (.vbs and .js) not far behind. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5997","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5922","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si5948","si5955","si5974","si5985","si6379","si6009","si6023","si6037","si6051","si5997"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5922"},"question":{"interactionId":"5935","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Ransomware is usually delivered in e-mails with malicious attachments. Which file extensions are dangerous?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6086","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6094","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6102","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6110","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6118","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6075","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6098","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6106","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6114","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6130","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6134","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6148","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6065","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6065"}}},{"id":"Privacy and Security Awareness Week","class":"project","title":"Privacy and Security Awareness Week","children":["Slide4365","Slide4471","Slide4635","Slide4778","Slide4921","Slide5064","Slide5207","Slide5350","Slide5493","Slide5636","Slide5779","Slide5922","Slide6065"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide4471q0","Slide4635q1","Slide4778q2","Slide4921q3","Slide5064q4","Slide5207q5","Slide5350q6","Slide5493q7","Slide5636q8","Slide5779q9","Slide5922q10"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":110,"passScore":88}}}],"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide4471","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide4635","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide4778","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide4921","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide5064","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide5207","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide5350","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide5493","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide5636","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide5779","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide5922","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide6065","title":"Slide 13"}]}